Richard Scarry Papers 1997.0048
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
Richard Scarry Papers
undated, 1946-1997.
1997.0048
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Libraries
106.3 Linear feet
The Richard Scarry Papers contain materials related to Scarry himself, but the majority of the archives pertains to the creation, production, and distribution of his books for children. The archives contains materials and correspondence concerning Scarry's early work, with Western Publishing and Little Golden Books, beginning in the 1950s. A greater amount of material concerns the works produced by Scarry during his later association with Random House.
Scarry, Richard.
Biography
Richard McClure Scarry was born June 5, 1919, in Boston, Massachussetts. Although an avid reader and artist as a child, Scarry was a lackluster student. After a failed attempt at business school, Scarry enrolled in Boston's Museum of Fine Arts School in 1939, but left the course unfinished when he was drafted in 1942.
The Army enrolled Scarry in Radio Repair School, but was soon tapped by his commanding officer to paint a sign. He completed Officer Candidate School and was later trained in Special Services, a unit dedicated to military morale and entertainment. From there, Scarry was assigned to the Information and Morale Section, Allied Forces Headquarters in North Africa as art director and promoted to Captain. There he published a newsletter for soldiers.
Scarry was discharged from the Army in March, 1946, and moved to New York City. After taking and leaving two jobs (one for in the art department of Vogue and the other at an advertising agency), Scarry became a free-lancer. During this time, he met Patricia (Patsy) Murphy, and married her in September, 1948.
In 1948, when Scarry's agent suggested he create a portfolio of illustrations for children's books, Scarry was offered and accepted a one-year renewable contract with Artists and Writers, a subsidiary of Western Publishing and Simon and Schuster, to create artwork for Golden storybooks and Little Golden Books. During 1949, Artists and Writers published six books with Scarry's illustrations.
In 1950, the Scarrys moved to Ridgefield, Connecticut, but their social network remained chiefly in New York City. In January, 1953, Richard Scarry, Jr., called Huck by his family and friends, was born.
Scarry's contract with Artists and Writers was renewed, and in 1951, Simon and Schuster published The Great Big Car and Truck Book, which Scarry both wrote and illustrated. In 1952, Artists and Writers offered him an exclusive contract until 1956. At the same time, Patsy Scarry began to write children's books, which Scarry illustrated. In 1955, Scarry negotiated new terms with Artists and Writers, which allowed him individual book contracts and royalties from his work. He continued to illustrate Little Golden books throughout the 1950s.
In 1959, the Scarry family bought a house in Westport, Connecticut, and attracted a wide circle of artistic and publishing friends. Because of monetary problems, Scarry sought work with other publishers, and began to publish the Tinker and Tanker series with Doubleday in 1960. Meanwhile, Scarry began to create what became Richard Scarry's Best Word Book Ever (1963). Its success engendered Richard Scarry's Busy, Busy World (1965) and Richard Scarry's Storybook Dictionary (1966).
[Note: This biography condenses the information found in The Busy, Busy World of Richard Scarry, which provides a very extensive and detailed biography (pages 9-120).
Scope and Content
The Richard Scarry Papers contain materials related to Scarry himself, but the majority of the archives pertains to the creation, production, and distribution of his books for children. The archives contains materials and correspondence concerning Scarry's early work, with Western Publishing and Little Golden Books, beginning in the 1950s. A greater amount of material concerns the works produced by Scarry during his later association with Random House.
Arrangement
The Richard Scarry Papers are arranged into four series.
Series I: Correspondence, undated, 1972-1996 contains letters, copies of letters, and faxed letters to and from Scarry.
Series II: Children's Literature, undated, 1965-1993 contains notes, manuscripts, drawings, separations, artwork, and articles pertinent to the creation of Scarry's many books. This series is arranged alphabetically by work.
Series III: Ephemera, 1989-1997 contains artifacts belonging to Scarry and some artifacts related to Scarry's books and/or characters.
Series IV: Personal Papers, 1946-1994 contains documents concerning Scarry's life and that of his family and friends.
Series V: Audiovisual materials, 19-- -1997 contains audio and video cassettes.
Separated Material
The following materials have been separated from the collection and cataloged:
Il Libro dei Mestieri [Italian version of What Do People Do All Day?] Dodd CLC D1103
Lowly Worm Car and Truck Book Dodd CLC D288
Best ABC Video Ever! 1997-0048.vr1
Educated Eye 1997-0048.vr2
Busy World of Richard Scarry Featurette 1997-0048.vr3
Christmas Stories 1997-0048.vr4
6 audio cassettes.
6 slides.
Selected Bibliography
Acquisition Information
The first portion of this collection was originally deposited in the archives in 1984 by Richard Scarry, via Ole Risom of Random House and Attorney Sydney Kramer. The collection at that time consisted of artwork for twenty-seven picture books, plus Random House's donation of most of the corresponding published books. The materials for the first deposit came to the archives from Random House. The deposit was donated to the archives in 1995 by Richard Scarry's estate.
Random House sent ten further portfolios of artwork, plus their corresponding books, to the archives in 1986. This first donation included approximately 1100 pieces of artwork for thirty-three of Scarry's books, plus the map cases to hold the artwork. A second donation of aproximately 484 pieces of art was given to the archives in 1996 by Ole and Agnes Risom, along with Attorney Stanley Garrett, who administered Scarry's estate. In 1997, Mr. Garrett and his wife Sonja also added to the collection. In 1998, Mr. and Mrs. Risom donated more original artwork, correspondence, recordings, and miscellaneous other materials to expand the collection.
In 2004, Deborah Pfeiffenberger of the New Britain Youth Museum donated the two stuffed dolls in Box 5 to the collection.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to children's literature and associated artwork. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the Reading Room desk.
Additional Scarry materials are located at the University of Southern Mississippi as part of the de Grummond Collection
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Benstead, Vivienne.; Cat, Huckle [fictitious character].; Cat, Sam [fictitious character].; Charlie, Able Baker [fictitious character].; Dale, Kathleen N.; Gale, Leah.; Goldbug [fictitious character].; Golden Press.; Hippo, Hilda [fictitious character].; Hozen, Barbara Shook.; Jackson, Kathryn.; Jacob, Leland B.; Little Golden Books.; Little Simon.; Miss Honey [fictitious character].; Mr. Fix-It [fictitious character].; Mr. Frumble [fictitious character].; Nolte, Nancy.; Osswald, Edith.; Pig Will [fictitious character].; Pig Won't [fictitious character].; Pig, Dudley [fictitious character].; Pig, Paint [fictitious character].; Pig, Patrick [fictitious character].; Pig, Peasant [fictitious character].; Pig, Postman [fictitious character].; Random House.; Reed, Mary.; Risom, Ole.; Scarry, Patricia M.; Scarry, Richard, Jr. (Huck); Scarry, Richard.; Scarry.; Simon and Schuster.; Tanker [fictitious character].; Tinker [fictitious character].; Turner, Jo Jasper.; United States Army.; Werner, Jane.; Western Publishing Company.; Worm, Lowly [ficitious character].; Zolotow, Charlotte.; Administrative Records.; Art director.; Artist.; Audio cassettes.; Audio visual materials.; Author.; Authors, American 20th century.; Book dummies.; Books.; Boston, Massachusetts.; Busytown [imaginary place].; Children's literature, American 20th century.; Children's literature--Illustrations.; Contracts.; Correspondence.; Financial Records.; Galley proofs.; Gstadd, Switzerland.; Illustrations (visual works).; Illustrator.; Lantern slides.; Lausanne, Switzerland.; Manuscripts.; New York, New York.; Northeast Children's Literature Collection.; Notes.; Obituaries.; Photocopies.; Photographs.; Posters.; Press releases.; Publications.; Ridgefield, Connecticut.; Sketches.; Soldier.; Stuffed toys.; Typescripts.; Videocassettes.; Westport, Connecticut.; Works of Art.; Workville [imaginary place].
- Series I: Correspondence, 1972-1996
  - Bush, Barbara, to Scarry, 1992 April 25 (Box 1:, Folder 1)
  - Gale Research to Scarry, 1983-1993 (Box 1:, Folder 2)
  - Gender portrayal in Scarry's books, 1972-1986 (Box 1:, Folder 3)
  - Health issues in Scarry's books, 1974-1976 (Box 1:, Folder 4)
  - Nodelman, Perry, to Scarry, 1989 October 10 (Box 1:, Folder 5)
  - Race portrayal in Scarry's books, 1986 (Box 1:, Folder 6)
  - Random House to Risom, Ole, 1989-1990 (Box 1:, Folder 7)
  - Random House to Scarry, 1990 May 7 (Box 1:, Folder 8)
  - Reagan, Nancy, to Scarry, 1988 May 19 (Box 1:, Folder 9)
  - Rosen, Barbara, to Scarry, 1992 March 20 (Box 1:, Folder 10)
  - Scarry to children's library, 1980 November (Box 1:, Folder 11)
  - Scarry to generic reader, undated (Box 1:, Folder 12)
  - Scarry to Risom, Ole, 1984-1994 (Box 1:, Folder 13)
  - Risom, Ole, to Scarry, undated (Box OS:, Folder 1293)
  - Scarry to Stevens, Norman, University of Connecticut Libraries, 1992 August 14 (Box 1:, Folder 14)
  - Scarry to Summit, Rovins, and Feldman, 1990 January 18 (Box 1:, Folder 15)
  - Scarry, Huck (Richard Jr.), to Scarry, 1993 March 9 (Box 1:, Folder 16)
  - Scarry, Patricia, to Risom, Ole, 1981-1994 (Box 1:, Folder 17)
  - University of Connecticut Libraries to Scarry, 1986-1992 (Box 1:, Folder 18)
  - University of Southern Mississippi Libraries to Scarry, 1981 August 8 (Box 1:, Folder 19)
  - Violence in Scarry's books, 1974 (Box 1:, Folder 20)
  - Western Publishing to Risom, Ole, 1996 April 9 (Box 1:, Folder 21)
  - Unidentified, to Risom, Ole, 1994 November 23 (Box 1:, Folder 22)
- Series II: Children's Literature, undated, 1965-1993
  - ABC, preliminary drawings, undated (Box OS:, Folder 1294)
  - ABC Word Book, 1971
    - Sketches (28 pieces), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 81)
    - Color separation (cover), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 82)
    - Color separation (pages 2-3), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 83)
    - Color separation (pages 4-5), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 84)
    - Color separation (pages 6-7), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 85)
    - Color separation (pages 8-9), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 86)
    - Color separation (pages 10-11), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 87)
    - Color separation (pages 12-13), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 88)
    - Color separation (pages 14-15), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 89)
    - Color separation (pages 16-17), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 90)
    - Color separation (pages 18-19), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 91)
    - Color separation (pages 20-21), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 92)
    - Color separation (pages 22-23), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 93)
    - Color separation (pages 24-25), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 94)
    - Color separation (pages 26-27), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 95)
    - Color separation (pages 28-29), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 96)
    - Color separation (pages 30-31), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 97)
    - Color separation (pages 32-33), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 98)
    - Color separation (pages 34-35), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 99)
    - Color separation (pages 36-37), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 100)
    - Color separation (pages 38-39), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 101)
    - Color separation (pages 40-41), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 102)
    - Color separation (pages 42-43), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 103)
    - Color separation (pages 44-45), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 104)
    - Color separation (pages 46-47), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 105)
    - Color separation (pages 48-49), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 106)
    - Color separation (pages 50-51), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 107)
    - Color separation (pages 52-53), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 108)
    - Color separation (pages 54-55), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 109)
    - Color separation (pages 56-57), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 110)
    - Color separation (pages 58-59), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 111)
    - Color separation (pages 60-61), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 112)
    - Black and white separation (cover), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 648)
    - Black and white separation (pages 2-3), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 649)
    - Black and white separation (pages 4-5), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 650)
    - Black and white separation (pages 6-7), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 651)
    - Black and white separation (pages 8-9), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 652)
    - Black and white separation and copy (from abridged version) (pages 10-11), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 653)
    - Black and white separation (pages 12-13), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 654)
    - Black and white separation (pages 14-15), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 655)
    - Black and white separation (pages 16-17), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 656)
    - Black and white separation (pages 18-19), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 657)
    - Black and white separation (pages 20-21), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 658)
    - Black and white separation (pages 22-23), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 659)
    - Black and white separation (pages 24-25), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 660)
    - Black and white separation (pages 26-27), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 661)
    - Black and white separation (pages 28-29), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 662)
    - Black and white separation (pages 30-31), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 663)
    - Black and white separation (pages 32-33), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 664)
    - Black and white separation (pages 34-35), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 665)
    - Black and white separation (pages 36-37), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 666)
    - Black and white separation (pages 38-39), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 667)
    - Black and white separation (pages 40-41), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 668)
    - Black and white separation (pages 42-43), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 669)
    - Black and white separation (pages 44-45), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 670)
    - Black and white separation (pages 46-47), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 671)
    - Black and white separation (pages 48-49), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 672)
    - Black and white separation (pages 50-51), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 673)
    - Black and white separation (pages 52-53), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 673a)
    - Black and white separation (pages 54-55), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 674)
    - Black and white separation (pages 56-57), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 675)
    - Black and white separation (pages 58-59), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 676)
    - Black and white separation (pages 60-61), ca. 1971 (Box OS:, Folder 677)
  - Book reviews, 1973-1977 (Box 1:, Folder 23)
  - Best Christmas Book Ever, 1981
    - Original black and white artwork (23 pieces), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 113)
    - Repro (page 3), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 114)
    - Separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 115)
    - Separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 116)
    - Separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 117)
    - Separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 118)
    - Separations (pages 10-11), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 119)
    - Separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 120)
    - Separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 121)
    - Separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 122)
    - Separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 123)
    - Separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 124)
    - Separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 125)
    - Separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 126)
    - Separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 127)
    - Separations (pages 28-29), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 128)
    - Separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 129)
    - Separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 130)
    - Separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 131)
    - Separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 132)
    - Separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 133)
    - Separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 134)
    - Separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 135)
    - Separations (pages 44-45), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 136)
    - Repro (page 46), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 137)
    - Separations (pages 46-47), ca. 1981 (Box OS:, Folder 138)
  - Best Counting Book Ever, 1975
    - Dummy (copy), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 138a)
    - Original black and white artwork (cover), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 139)
    - Original black and white artwork (title page, 2 pieces), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 140)
    - Original black and white artwork (end papers), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 141)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 4-5), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 142)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 6-7), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 143)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 8-9), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 144)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 10-11), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 145)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 12-13), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 146)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 14-15), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 147)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 16-17), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 148)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 18-19), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 149)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 20-21), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 150)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 22-23), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 151)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 24-25), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 152)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 26-27), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 153)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 28-29), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 154)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 30-31), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 155)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 32-33), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 156)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 34-45), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 157)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 36-37), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 158)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 38-39), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 159)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 40-41), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 160)
    - Original black and white artwork (pages 42-43), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 161)
    - Original artwork (unused end papers), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 162)
    - Original black and white artwork (unused title page), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 163)
    - Color separation and blue board (cover), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 164)
    - Separations (front cover), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 165)
    - Alternate cover sketches (5 pieces), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 166)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 2-3), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 167)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 4-5), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 168)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 6-7), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 169)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 8-9), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 170)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 10-11), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 171)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 12-13), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 172)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 14-15), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 173)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 16-17), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 174)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 18-19), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 175)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 20-21), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 176)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 22-23), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 177)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 24-25), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 178)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 26-27), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 179)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 28-29), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 180)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 30-31), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 181)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 32-33), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 182)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 34-35), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 183)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 36-37), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 184)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 38-39), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 185)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 40-41), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 186)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 42-43), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 187)
    - Separations and blue board (pages 44-45), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 188)
    - Black and white art and blurb (back cover), ca. 1975 (Box OS:, Folder 189)
  - Best First Book Ever, 1979
    - Preliminary layout drawings (48 pieces), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 190)
    - Separations (front cover), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 191)
    - Separations (back cover), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 192)
    - Separations (pages 2-3), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 193)
    - Separations (pages 4-5), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 203)
    - Separations (pages 6-7), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 194)
    - Separations (pages 8-9), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 195)
    - Separations (pages 12-13), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 196)
    - Separations (pages 14-15), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 197)
    - Separations (pages 16-17), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 204)
    - Separations (pages 18-19), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 205)
    - Separations (pages 20-21), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 198)
    - Separations (pages 22-23), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 199)
    - Small separations (pages 22-23, back cover), ca. 1979 (Box OS:)
    - Separations (pages 24-25), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 201)
    - Separations (pages 26-27), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 206)
    - Separations (pages 30-31), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 207)
    - Separations (pages 32-33), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 202)
    - Separations (pages 34-35), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 208)
    - Separations (pages 36-37), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 209)
    - Separations (pages 38-39), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 210)
    - Separations (pages 40-41), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 211)
    - Separations (pages 42-43), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 212)
    - Separations (pages 44-45), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 213)
    - Separations (pages 46-47), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 214)
    - Black and white separation (front cover), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 678)
    - Black and white separation (back cover), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 679)
    - Black and white separation (pages 2-3), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 680)
    - Black and white separation (pages 4-5), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 681)
    - Black and white separation (pages 6-7), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 682)
    - Black and white separation (pages 8-9), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 683)
    - Black and white separation (pages 10-11), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 684)
    - Black and white separation (pages 12-13), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 685)
    - Black and white separation (pages 16-17), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 686)
    - Black and white separation (pages 18-19), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 687)
    - Black and white separation (pages 20-21), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 688)
    - Black and white separation (pages 22-23), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 689)
    - Black and white separation (pages 22-23), ca. 1979 (Box OS:, Folder 690)
      General note
      There are two separations labelled pages 22 and 23.